{
    "id": "04ba4c8c54f74cd3aadfa688bb8610ed",
    "title": "Present Continuous Tense Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Jane …………………. in the garden.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "works",
                "is working",
                "are working"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7d254462404346088b1edeff229092c6"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………….. Oliver Twist at the moment.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is reading",
                "am reading",
                "are reading"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e254141d6aaf4b2fa227756778912eb2"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………… TV.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is watching",
                "am watching",
                "are watching"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "20550b4a8bc64d1b928b9b410bdad27a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who ……………….. the violin?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is playing",
                "are playing",
                "am playing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2faeb460d7874aeb8f7eda84efe2484d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Don’t make noise. The baby …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is sleeping",
                "are sleeping",
                "am sleeping"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "74109be7a8ba4ca78e6920d53d7cfa80"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………… in the park now.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is waiting",
                "am waiting",
                "are waiting"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a80c5fd5c5af4ae9a89a3a2330801057"
        },
        {
            "question": "Jane and Susie ………………… in the kitchen.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is cooking",
                "are cooking",
                "am cooking"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "482d500fa9c04c6c87ae8f23f02cc7c1"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………… pizza at the moment.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is making",
                "are making",
                "am making"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8d198105f7de48e7ab8057dac316df0b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Mother ………………….. a sweater.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is knitting",
                "are knitting",
                "am knitting"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3c01aed33ab84c7a8d27b6edf4d2fc59"
        },
        {
            "question": "Susan and her friend …………………. over for lunch.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is coming",
                "are coming",
                "am coming"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4749b26e1c93478c9036c38c78757551"
        }
    ]
}